# William Santosa

Santa Cruz, CA 95060 | (925) 208-8791 | williamwsantosa@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/williamsantosa

#### **SUMMARY**

Second-year student with Junior standing majoring in Computer Science at University of California, Santa Cruz with the Dean's Honor throughout all of university (2020 & 2021). Has 10 years of experience in leadership including customer/ personal interaction in martial arts, experienced logistical processes at Amazon Warehouse, and organized Science Olympiad at a state level. Is certified with AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and proficient in Python, Java, C, and AWS services. Has exposure to SAP ABAP, SAP S/4 Hana Cloud solution, C++, and Lua.

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, GPA: 4.00

Expected to graduate in 2023

Awards: Dean's Honor Fall 2020, Winter 2021, Spring 2021, Fall 2021

Coursework: Computer Architecture, Computer Systems, C Programming, Assembly Language, Calculus, Discrete Math, Abstractions, Linear Algebra

#### **Dougherty Valley High School**

San Ramon, CA

Student, GPA: 3.96

Aug 2016 – June 2020

# **Stanford University**

Stanford, CA

Student June 2019 - Aug 2019

Coursework: Mathematical Foundations in Computing

Participated in "Silicon Valley Innovation Academy" where a limited selection of Summer Session students develop and present a team-based moonshot project to the public and the community.

**Amazon Web Services** Online

Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner Certification

July 2021 - Aug 2021

Obtained basic understanding of IT services and their uses in the AWS Cloud platform as well as knowledge of core AWS services and their use cases, billing and pricing models, security concepts, and how cloud concepts impact businesses.

SAP Academy Online

SAP ABAP Dialog Programming BC 100 & SAP S/4 HANA Cloud Solution

2019

Obtained basic understanding of ABAP programming and S/4HANA Cloud for achieving business growth, real-time analytics, artificial intelligence, and machine learning.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

College Nine Peer Navigator

June 2021 - Dec 2021

- Introduced freshmen to college and gave advice on how to succeed in their first year
- Held office hours for students that needed help with navigating the university or homework
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

#### Koo's Martial Arts

Instructor & Coach

San Ramon, CA

July 2017 - Aug 2021

- Introduced students to the forms, techniques, and hard-working philosophy of Taekwondo
  - Taught students the importance of hard-work, self-study, and discipline

Amazon Warehouse Tracy, CA

Warehouse Team Member

June 2021 – Aug 2021

• Packed, stocked, and organized inventory

# **Baskin School of Engineering at UCSC**

Online

Computer Systems & C Programming Reader

Mar 2021 – June 2021

- Helped students with problem solving and difficult concepts such as depth first search and recursion
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Amazon Web Services Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner  AWARDS	Online Aug 2021		
		University of California, Santa Cruz	2020 - 2021
		Dean's Honors	
California Taekwondo Foundation	2019		
Legacy – Honoring the Leaders of Taekwondo			
World Taekwondo Foundation & California Taekwondo Foundation	2016		

Silver Leadership Award

White House 2015

President's Education Award

#### **INTERESTS**

International travel, gym, anime, martial arts, and video games